onlineappsforpc.com 2016-06-05

# Privacy Policy – Online Apps For PC

## Privacy Policy of OnlineAppsForPC.com

If you require any information or have any questions regarding our privacy policy, feel free to contact us using contact forum here.

At _**Online** **AppsForPC.com**_ , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us and we take it very seriously. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information like the pages you visit and which links you click, which ads you see and click on and the categories of search terms you enter when you visit our blog. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

### Log Files

Like other blogs/websites , _ **Online** ** _A_ ppsForPC.com**_ makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit page, gather demographic information, IP addresses and the other such information not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit toyour sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on _**OnlineAppsForPC.com**_  send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/ or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

**_OnlineAppsForPC.com_**  has no access to or control over the cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.
